[
  {
    "index": 0,
    "question": "Like a child ... lost its mother",
    "answer": "chicken"
  },
  {
    "index": 1,
    "question": "Like water in ... taro",
    "answer": "leaf"
  },
  {
    "index": 2,
    "question": "Life is conceived ... death is in the ground",
    "answer": "custom"
  },
  {
    "index": 3,
    "question": "Far in ... , close at heart",
    "answer": "eyes"
  },
  {
    "index": 4,
    "question": "There is no rattan ... so",
    "answer": "root"
  },
  {
    "index": 5,
    "question": "Gold debt may be paid, Debt ... taken to death",
    "answer": "mind"
  },
  {
    "index": 6,
    "question": "There is a shrimp behind ... ",
    "answer": "stone"
  },
  {
    "index": 7,
    "question": "There are ... there are ants",
    "answer": "sugar"
  },
  {
    "index": 8,
    "question": "There is ... there is fire",
    "answer": "smoke"
  },
  {
    "index": 9,
    "question": "Like ... and the sky",
    "answer": "earth"
  },
  {
    "index": 10,
    "question": "Rather than rain ... in the land of others, it is better to rain stones in one's own country",
    "answer": "gold"
  },
  {
    "index": 11,
    "question": "Given ... asked for a heart",
    "answer": "heart"
  },
  {
    "index": 12,
    "question": " ... hole cover hole",
    "answer": "Dig"
  },
  {
    "index": 13,
    "question": "Warm warm ... chicken",
    "answer": "poop"
  },
  {
    "index": 14,
    "question": "Save basic... , diligent but smart",
    "answer": "rich"
  },
  {
    "index": 15,
    "question": " ... ask astray on the road",
    "answer": "Shame"
  },
  {
    "index": 16,
    "question": " ... has become mush",
    "answer": "Rice"
  },
  {
    "index": 17,
    "question": "The shoot of being loved ... has arrived",
    "answer": "ulama"
  },
  {
    "index": 18,
    "question": "Like science ... the more contained the more bent down",
    "answer": "paddy"
  },
  {
    "index": 19,
    "question": "Keg ... loud sound",
    "answer": "empty"
  },
  {
    "index": 20,
    "question": "Weapon eats ... ",
    "answer": "master"
  },
  {
    "index": 21,
    "question": "No ivory ... no crack",
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "index": 22,
    "question": "There is no rattan, not even roots ... ",
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "index": 23,
    "question": "Require ... to the land of China",
    "answer": "science"
  },
  {
    "index": 24,
    "question": "Nothing ... even roots",
    "answer": "rattan"
  },
  {
    "index": 25,
    "question": "Bigger ... than the pole",
    "answer": "stake"
  },
  {
    "index": 26,
    "question": "Out of sight ... in the heart",
    "answer": "close"
  },
  {
    "index": 27,
    "question": "As clever as ... jump, sometimes fall too",
    "answer": "squirrel"
  },
  {
    "index": 28,
    "question": "Destroyed ... conceived by the ground, kindness is remembered too",
    "answer": "body"
  },
  {
    "index": 29,
    "question": "United we ... , divided we fall",
    "answer": "firm"
  },
  {
    "index": 30,
    "question": "Large stake than ...",
    "answer": "pole"
  },
  {
    "index": 31,
    "question": "So sweet ... thrown away",
    "answer": "sepah"
  },
  {
    "index": 32,
    "question": "Save the base rich, ... base smart",
    "answer": "diligent"
  },
  {
    "index": 33,
    "question": "Live ... don't want to / don't want to die",
    "answer": "reluctant"
  },
  {
    "index": 34,
    "question": "Because a speck of indigo, ... a can of milk",
    "answer": "broken"
  },
  {
    "index": 35,
    "question": "Different fields of grasshoppers, different ... different fish",
    "answer": "bottom"
  },
  {
    "index": 36,
    "question": "Lick ... myself",
    "answer": "spit"
  },
  {
    "index": 37,
    "question": "Fishing in the water ... ",
    "answer": "muddy"
  },
  {
    "index": 38,
    "question": " ... eat plants",
    "answer": "Fence"
  },
  {
    "index": 39,
    "question": "Like a horse ... from the edge",
    "answer": "let go"
  },
  {
    "index": 40,
    "question": "Water rippled no ... ",
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "index": 41,
    "question": "The rooster crows the day ... ",
    "answer": "afternoon"
  },
  {
    "index": 42,
    "question": "Like water on a leaf ... ",
    "answer": "taro"
  },
  {
    "index": 43,
    "question": "Like ... in a shell",
    "answer": "frog"
  },
  {
    "index": 44,
    "question": "Where the earth is ... there the sky is upheld",
    "answer": "step"
  },
  {
    "index": 45,
    "question": "Teacher pees standing up, ... pees running",
    "answer": "student"
  },
  {
    "index": 46,
    "question": "Small chili ...",
    "answer": "cayenne"
  },
  {
    "index": 47,
    "question": "Already ... hit the stairs",
    "answer": "fall"
  },
  {
    "index": 48,
    "question": "While diving ... water",
    "answer": "drink"
  },
  {
    "index": 49,
    "question": "Like a chicken lost ... ",
    "answer": "parent"
  },
  {
    "index": 50,
    "question": "Prepare umbrella before ...",
    "answer": "rain"
  },
  {
    "index": 51,
    "question": "Little by little over time it becomes ... ",
    "answer": "hill"
  },
  {
    "index": 52,
    "question": " ... die in the rice field",
    "answer": "Rat"
  },
  {
    "index": 53,
    "question": " ... down blunt up",
    "answer": "Sharp"
  },
  {
    "index": 54,
    "question": " ... is money",
    "answer": "Time"
  },
  {
    "index": 55,
    "question": "The storm ... passed",
    "answer": "sure"
  },
  {
    "index": 56,
    "question": " ... in a blanket",
    "answer": "enemy"
  },
  {
    "index": 57,
    "question": "A year old corn, ... a handful of betel nut",
    "answer": "blood"
  },
  {
    "index": 58,
    "question": "Like ... in a cage",
    "answer": "bird"
  },
  {
    "index": 59,
    "question": "There is money there ... ",
    "answer": "item"
  },
  {
    "index": 60,
    "question": "Water ... not deep mark",
    "answer": "ripple"
  },
  {
    "index": 61,
    "question": "Like ... halved",
    "answer": "betel nut"
  },
  {
    "index": 62,
    "question": "Silence ... language",
    "answer": "a thousand"
  },
  {
    "index": 63,
    "question": "Tigers die leaving ... , elephants die leaving tusks",
    "answer": "stripe"
  },
  {
    "index": 64,
    "question": "...forgetting the skin",
    "answer": "Beans"
  },
  {
    "index": 65,
    "question": " ... stone hiding hand",
    "answer": "Throw"
  },
  {
    "index": 66,
    "question": "Water ... washes away",
    "answer": "calm down"
  },
  {
    "index": 67,
    "question": "Arrived not picked up ... not delivered",
    "answer": "home"
  },
  {
    "index": 68,
    "question": "From ... clear water will not flow cloudy",
    "answer": "pond"
  },
  {
    "index": 69,
    "question": " ... the body contained in the good land is also remembered",
    "answer": "Destroyed"
  },
  {
    "index": 70,
    "question": " ... stone hiding hand",
    "answer": "Throw"
  },
  {
    "index": 71,
    "question": " ... hairy chicken",
    "answer": "Weasel"
  },
  {
    "index": 72,
    "question": "Nothing ... that is not cracked",
    "answer": "ivory"
  },
  {
    "index": 73,
    "question": "Elderly ... the older the more",
    "answer": "caladium"
  },
  {
    "index": 74,
    "question": "Same weight... , light weight and carry",
    "answer": "to bear"
  },
  {
    "index": 75,
    "question": "Like ... miss the moon",
    "answer": "back"
  },
  {
    "index": 76,
    "question": "Milk ... with tubal water",
    "answer": "reply"
  },
  {
    "index": 77,
    "question": "Like a bird in ...",
    "answer": "cage"
  },
  {
    "index": 78,
    "question": "Learning indiscriminately is like a flower... it doesn't work",
    "answer": "flower"
  },
  {
    "index": 79,
    "question": "The dog barks the caravan ... ",
    "answer": "pass"
  },
  {
    "index": 80,
    "question": "The world is not ... Moringa leaves",
    "answer": "wide"
  },
  {
    "index": 81,
    "question": "Elephant in ... invisible eye, ant across the sea visible",
    "answer": "huddle"
  },
  {
    "index": 82,
    "question": "Elephant dies leaving tusks, ... dies leaving stripes",
    "answer": "tiger"
  },
  {
    "index": 83,
    "question": "Patted the water in the pan, splashed in the face...",
    "answer": "alone"
  },
  {
    "index": 84,
    "question": "Like areca nut ... two",
    "answer": "split"
  },
  {
    "index": 85,
    "question": "Like water in ... taro",
    "answer": "leaf"
  },
  {
    "index": 86,
    "question": "From the bush to ... ",
    "answer": "grove"
  },
  {
    "index": 87,
    "question": "Instead of living in the mirror... , it is better to die under the ground",
    "answer": "carcass"
  },
  {
    "index": 88,
    "question": "End of ... sepah thrown away",
    "answer": "sweet"
  },
  {
    "index": 89,
    "question": "Far in ... , close at heart",
    "answer": "eyes"
  },
  {
    "index": 90,
    "question": "I mean... the mountain, can't my hand reach it",
    "answer": "hug"
  },
  {
    "index": 91,
    "question": "Shame ... lost on the road",
    "answer": "ask"
  },
  {
    "index": 92,
    "question": "While ... drinking water",
    "answer": "diving"
  },
  {
    "index": 93,
    "question": "There is a brother's money in ... , no brother's money is floating",
    "answer": "darling"
  },
  {
    "index": 94,
    "question": "Milk is answered with ... ",
    "answer": "tubal water"
  },
  {
    "index": 95,
    "question": "Beans forget about ... ",
    "answer": "skin"
  },
  {
    "index": 96,
    "question": " ... saliva",
    "answer": "lick"
  },
  {
    "index": 97,
    "question": " ... hunting/in fleece",
    "answer": "Wolf"
  },
  {
    "index": 98,
    "question": "The tongue is not ... ",
    "answer": "bony"
  },
  {
    "index": 99,
    "question": "As long as life is still in the body",
    "answer": "uterus"
  },
  {
    "index": 100,
    "question": "Don't ... in murky water",
    "answer": "mirror"
  },
  {
    "index": 101,
    "question": "As long as the yellow leaf is not... , then I will always chase you to get your love",
    "answer": "curved"
  },
  {
    "index": 102,
    "question": "Like eating ... simalakama",
    "answer": "fruit"
  }
]
